练习 1-52：描述性短语和固定短语，《金发姑娘》。请读这个故事。
Exercise 1-52. Descriptions and Set Phrases. Goldilocks. Read the story and
重读标出的词，判断它们是描述性短语、固定短语，还是对比。
stress the indicated words. Notice if they're a description, a set phrase, or
第三类是对比；下面开始跟读故事。
contrast. Repeat after me. There's a little girl. Her name is Goldilocks. She's
in a sunny forest. She sees a small house. She knocks on the door, but no one
answers. She goes inside. In the large room, there are three chairs. Goldilocks
sits on the biggest chair, but it's too high. She sits on the middle-sized one,
but it's too low. She sits on the small chair, and it's just right. On the table,
There are three bowls. There's hot porridge in the bowls. She tries the first
one, but it's too hot. The second one is too cold. And the third one is just right.
So she eats it all. After that, she goes upstairs. She looks around. There are
three beds. so she sits down. The biggest bed is too hard. The middle-sized bed is
too soft. The little one is just right, so she lies down. Soon she falls asleep. In
the meantime, the family of three bears comes home. The papa bear, the mama bear,
and the baby bear. They look around. They say, who's been sitting in our chairs and
eating our porridge? Then they run upstairs. They say, who's been sleeping in
our beds? Goldilocks wakes up. She's very scared. She runs away. Goldilocks never
comes back.